{
  "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon:pikachu",
  "name": "Pikachu",
  "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
  "baseStats": {
    "hp": 35,
    "attack": 55,
    "speed": 90,
    "spAttack": 50
  },
  "types": [
    "pokeemerald:type:electric"
  ],
  "catchRate": 190,
  "evYield": {
    "speed": 2
  },
  "genderRatio": 127,
  "eggCycles": 10,
  "eggGroups": [
    "pokeemerald:egg_group:field",
    "pokeemerald:egg_group:fairy"
  ],
  "friendship": 70,
  "growthRate": "pokeemerald:growth_rate:medium_fast",
  "abilities": [
    "pokeemerald:ability:static",
    null,
    "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
  ],
  "bodyColor": "pokeemerald:body_color:yellow",
  "categoryId": "pokeemerald:category:mouse",
  "height": 4,
  "weight": 60,
  "evolutions": [
    {
      "method": "pokeemerald:evolution_method:item",
      "parameterName": "ITEM_THUNDER_STONE",
      "targetSpeciesId": "pokeemerald:pokemon:raichu"
    },
    {
      "method": "pokeemerald:evolution_method:item",
      "parameterName": "ITEM_THUNDER_STONE",
      "targetSpeciesId": "pokeemerald:pokemon:raichu-alola"
    }
  ],
  "levelUpMoves": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:nuzzle"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:nasty_plot"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:charm"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:sweet_kiss"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:play_nice"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:quick_attack"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:tail_whip"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:thunder_shock"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:growl"
    },
    {
      "level": 4,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:thunder_wave"
    },
    {
      "level": 8,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:double_team"
    },
    {
      "level": 12,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:electro_ball"
    },
    {
      "level": 16,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:feint"
    },
    {
      "level": 20,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:spark"
    },
    {
      "level": 24,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:agility"
    },
    {
      "level": 28,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:iron_tail"
    },
    {
      "level": 32,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:discharge"
    },
    {
      "level": 36,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:thunderbolt"
    },
    {
      "level": 40,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:light_screen"
    },
    {
      "level": 44,
      "moveId": "pokeemerald:move:thunder"
    }
  ],
  "teachableMoves": [
    "pokeemerald:move:attract",
    "pokeemerald:move:body_slam",
    "pokeemerald:move:brick_break",
    "pokeemerald:move:calm_mind",
    "pokeemerald:move:counter",
    "pokeemerald:move:defense_curl",
    "pokeemerald:move:dig",
    "pokeemerald:move:double_edge",
    "pokeemerald:move:double_team",
    "pokeemerald:move:dynamic_punch",
    "pokeemerald:move:endure",
    "pokeemerald:move:facade",
    "pokeemerald:move:flash",
    "pokeemerald:move:focus_punch",
    "pokeemerald:move:iron_tail",
    "pokeemerald:move:light_screen",
    "pokeemerald:move:mega_kick",
    "pokeemerald:move:mega_punch",
    "pokeemerald:move:mud_slap",
    "pokeemerald:move:protect",
    "pokeemerald:move:rain_dance",
    "pokeemerald:move:reflect",
    "pokeemerald:move:rest",
    "pokeemerald:move:rock_smash",
    "pokeemerald:move:rollout",
    "pokeemerald:move:seismic_toss",
    "pokeemerald:move:shock_wave",
    "pokeemerald:move:sleep_talk",
    "pokeemerald:move:snore",
    "pokeemerald:move:strength",
    "pokeemerald:move:surf",
    "pokeemerald:move:swagger",
    "pokeemerald:move:swift",
    "pokeemerald:move:thief",
    "pokeemerald:move:thunder",
    "pokeemerald:move:thunderbolt",
    "pokeemerald:move:thunder_punch",
    "pokeemerald:move:thunder_wave",
    "pokeemerald:move:toxic"
  ],
  "sprites": {
    "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachufront",
    "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachufrontshiny",
    "frontFemale": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachufrontfemale",
    "frontFemaleShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachufrontfemaleshiny",
    "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuback",
    "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubackshiny",
    "backFemale": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubackfemale",
    "backFemaleShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubackfemaleshiny",
    "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuicon",
    "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoverworld",
    "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoverworldshiny"
  },
  "hasGenderDifferences": true,
  "forms": [
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/starter",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "starter",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 45,
        "attack": 80,
        "defense": 50,
        "speed": 120,
        "spAttack": 75,
        "spDefense": 60
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustarterfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustarterfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustarterback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustarterbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustartericon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustarteroverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachustarteroverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/gmax",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "gmax",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachugmaxoverworldshiny"
      },
      "formType": "pokeemerald:form_type:gigantamax",
      "transformMethod": "pokeemerald:transform_method:gigantamax"
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/world",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "world",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuworldoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/partner",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "partner",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartnerfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartnerfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartnerback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartnerbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartnericon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartneroverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupartneroverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/alola",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "alola",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolafront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolafrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolaback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolabackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolaicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolaoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachualolaoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/kalos",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "kalos",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachukalosoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/unova",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "unova",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovafront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovafrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovaback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovabackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovaicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovaoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuunovaoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/sinnoh",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "sinnoh",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachusinnohoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/hoenn",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "hoenn",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuhoennoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/original",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "original",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginalfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginalfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginalback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginalbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginalicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginaloverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuoriginaloverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/libre",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "libre",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibrefront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibrefrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibreback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibrebackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibreicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibreoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachulibreoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/phd",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "phd",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachuphdoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/pop-star",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "pop-star",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstarfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstarfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstarback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstarbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstaricon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstaroverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachupopstaroverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/belle",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "belle",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubellefront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubellefrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubelleback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubellebackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubelleicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubelleoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachubelleoverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/rock-star",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "rock-star",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstarfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstarfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstarback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstarbackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstaricon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstaroverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachurockstaroverworldshiny"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "pokeemerald:pokemon_form:pikachu/cosplay",
      "name": "Pikachu",
      "cryId": "pokeemerald:audio:sfx/cries/pikachu",
      "formKey": "cosplay",
      "baseStats": {
        "hp": 35,
        "attack": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "spAttack": 50
      },
      "types": [
        "pokeemerald:type:electric"
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "pokeemerald:ability:static",
        null,
        "pokeemerald:ability:lightning_rod"
      ],
      "sprites": {
        "front": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplayfront",
        "frontShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplayfrontshiny",
        "back": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplayback",
        "backShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplaybackshiny",
        "icon": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplayicon",
        "overworld": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplayoverworld",
        "overworldShiny": "pokeemerald:pokemon:sprite/pikachu/pikachucosplayoverworldshiny"
      }
    }
  ]
}